{
  "extraDescription": "NB: second operand is never negative",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "8 + 0",
      "answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "question": "10 &minus; 12",
      "answer": "-2"
    },
    {
      "question": "2 + 1",
      "answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "-4 &minus; 8",
      "answer": "-12"
    },
    {
      "question": "3 &minus; 12",
      "answer": "-9"
    },
    {
      "question": "4 &minus; 6",
      "answer": "-2"
    },
    {
      "question": "11 + 9",
      "answer": "20"
    },
    {
      "question": "12 &minus; 11",
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "-2 &minus; 7",
      "answer": "-9"
    },
    {
      "question": "10 &minus; 11",
      "answer": "-1"
    },
    {
      "question": "4 + 0",
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 9",
      "answer": "15"
    },
    {
      "question": "-6 + 6",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "-11 &minus; 10",
      "answer": "-21"
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 9",
      "answer": "17"
    },
    {
      "question": "11 + 2",
      "answer": "13"
    },
    {
      "question": "0 &minus; 5",
      "answer": "-5"
    },
    {
      "question": "-7 + 5",
      "answer": "-2"
    },
    {
      "question": "-6 + 11",
      "answer": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "2 + 8",
      "answer": "10"
    },
    {
      "question": "6 &minus; 2",
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "1 &minus; 4",
      "answer": "-3"
    },
    {
      "question": "6 &minus; 0",
      "answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "question": "-11 + 9",
      "answer": "-2"
    },
    {
      "question": "-2 + 6",
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "-12 &minus; 9",
      "answer": "-21"
    },
    {
      "question": "-4 + 8",
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "2 &minus; 6",
      "answer": "-4"
    },
    {
      "question": "1 + 1",
      "answer": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "-4 &minus; 7",
      "answer": "-11"
    },
    {
      "question": "-10 + 8",
      "answer": "-2"
    },
    {
      "question": "2 + 12",
      "answer": "14"
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + 5",
      "answer": "15"
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 3",
      "answer": "11"
    },
    {
      "question": "-4 &minus; 12",
      "answer": "-16"
    },
    {
      "question": "12 + 9",
      "answer": "21"
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + 9",
      "answer": "19"
    },
    {
      "question": "0 &minus; 9",
      "answer": "-9"
    },
    {
      "question": "0 &minus; 1",
      "answer": "-1"
    },
    {
      "question": "9 &minus; 7",
      "answer": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "1 + 12",
      "answer": "13"
    },
    {
      "question": "-2 &minus; 9",
      "answer": "-11"
    },
    {
      "question": "10 &minus; 7",
      "answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "4 &minus; 11",
      "answer": "-7"
    },
    {
      "question": "4 + 5",
      "answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "question": "9 &minus; 9",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 1",
      "answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "question": "-3 + 4",
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "-5 + 10",
      "answer": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "10 &minus; 4",
      "answer": "6"
    }
  ]
}
